All men want justice. Few are willing to pay the price.
The Jack Bull is a western, tv movie film directed by John Badham.
When the law fails to punish a fellow rancher that has abused his horses, a
Wyoming horse trader sacrifices it all in a quest for justice.
Myrl Redding, played by John Cusack.
Judge Tolliver, played by John Goodman.
Henry Ballard, played by L.Q. Jones.
Cora Redding, played by Miranda Otto.
Slater, played by John Savage.
Shelby Dykes, played by Rex Linn.
The Jack Bull is a 1999 American Western television film directed by John Badham and written by
Dick Cusack, loosely inspired by Heinrich von Kleist's 1810 novel Michael Kohlhaas.
It stars John Cusack, John Goodman, L.
Jones, Miranda Otto, and John C.
McGinley, and aired on HBO on April 17, 1999.
Much of the movie was filmed at the CL Ranch and the Heritage
Park Historical Village in Calgary, Alberta.
The film explores themes of wyoming, usa, justice, horse trader.